mustseeindia.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy & Opt Out

This Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information collected by www.mustseeindia.com, ("MSI"), when you access the website MSI . This policy does not apply to any entity not owned or controlled by the Company. This Policy may not be applicable to any information provided by you or on your behalf to MSI in any other context. By accessing the MSI website or any website of the Company, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy. 

**Collection of identifiable information**   
We will collect information from you if you choose to register for certain services provided by MSI . The following specific information will be sought by us when requesting information about you: Name, Age/Date of Birth, Gender, Marital Status, Anniversary, Occupation, E-mail address, Holiday Preferences. 

MSI uses the personal information collected from you for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain information, products and services; and to contact you about the latest about MSI. 

**Collection of non-identifiable information**   
This website may also provide us with certain non-personally identifiable information about your access to the website. Such information includes the IP address through which this site is accessed, the time at which this site is accessed and the specific portions of the website accessed by you. This information is not personally identifiable. 

MSI uses this information as a feedback for improvement of the website, and for an analysis of the most frequently accessed portions of the website. This information will not at any stage be passed on to any person. 

**Usage of cookies**   
The website uses cookies to improve your interactive sessions and to save time during access. When you return to the website, the information previously provided by you may be retrieved by your computer to enable certain features of the site without having to re-sign in, and allow you easier access to parts of the website customised by you. The cookie would allow you to automatically sign in when you access MSI, until you sign out. The cookie would be stored on the hard disk of your computer and would not be available for access by us. 

The acceptance of cookies is dependent on the browser settings on the web-browser used by you. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**   
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone, nor will we use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. 

We will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

a. We have your consent to share the information. 

b. We need to share the information with business partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve any issue. 

c. We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer. 

d. If required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to / reply to any court orders / legal process / summons served on MSI 

**Usage by our partners**   
We may from time to time engage external agencies to provide certain services on our behalf. These services may range from booking of any service offered on this website, sending dispatches by mail, co-ordination of feedback, delivery of prizes (if any) etc. These external agencies are obligated to us in terms of confidentiality agreements and will be provided the personal information strictly on a need to know basis. 

**Collection of information by third parties**   
MSI may offer promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information and we encourage you to consult their privacy policies for more information on their privacy practices. 

**Browsing history**

By using website **www.mustseeindia.com** , you consent to collection, storage, and use of your browsing history on this website. We share this information with trusted 3rd parties that use it to show you marketing communications of interest only. While no Personally Identifiable Information is shared, we respect your right to privacy hence this transparent disclosure. In addition, we respect your right to opt out. If you want to opt out from this program, please click here.   
In addition, most setup your browser software to reject 3rd party cookies. In addition, you can opt out of several similar programs by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) gateway opt-out site. 

**Advertisement**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Amendment of this policy**   
MSI may from time to time amend this policy. The latest version of this policy will reside on this website. In the event the amendment of this policy results in an enlargement of the scope of permitted disclosures of personally identifiable information, we shall obtain your consent before such disclosure. 

If you have questions about our privacy statement or our use of your information, or if you need help changing the information provided to us, please contact us by clicking [here](http://www.mustseeindia.com/contact).
